<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Digitramp 3.0</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Digitramp 3.0</description>
    <image>
      <title>Digitramp 3.0</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.126.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Digitramp Contributors</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:50:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CodeArena: Earn Through Coding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/codearena/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:50:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/codearena/</guid>
      <description>Why? In the landscape of alternative income opportunities, the digital realm offers a plethora of options for those skilled in coding. CodeArena stands out as a platform that not only allows developers to hone their skills but also to earn money through coding challenges. It leverages the competitive spirit of coding by hosting contests where the best solutions are rewarded. This platform is particularly appealing for programmers looking to monetize their skills, engage in healthy competition, and gain recognition in the developer community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Money &amp; Reduce Food Waste</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/too-good-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 23:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/too-good-to-go/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Too Good To Go&amp;rdquo; is an innovative app designed to combat food waste while offering consumers the opportunity to purchase food at significantly reduced prices. This guide explores why the app is beneficial, how to use it effectively, and what you can expect in terms of savings and environmental impact.
Why? Combat Food Waste Every year, millions of tons of food are wasted due to surplus production, unsold goods, and stringent sell-by date regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Cuponera</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/la-cuponera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 22:50:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/la-cuponera/</guid>
      <description>Your Guide to Smart Shopping In today&amp;rsquo;s digital era, where the cost of living continues to rise, finding ways to save money has become more important than ever. This is where &amp;ldquo;La Cuponera&amp;rdquo; comes into play—a revolutionary app designed to make the most out of every shopping experience by offering a wide range of discounts and deals right at your fingertips. But why should you consider adding yet another app to your collection?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking rewards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/walking-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 15:50:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/walking-money/</guid>
      <description>App Name Rewards &amp;amp; Earnings Platform Availability Estimated Income Fit For Bucks Redeemable rewards for steps iOS and Android Varies CashWalk 100 steps = 1 coin, max 100 coins/day iOS and Android ~$0.28/day Winwalk 1 coin per 100 steps, 100 coins/day limit Android only Similar to CashWalk Paidtogo Up to $75/month, $0.10 per mile iOS only Up to $75/month Miles Rewards for transportation, including walking iOS and Android Dependent on activity Paceline Rewards for heart rate elevation iOS only Based on activity Rover Average $15/hour for dog walking iOS and Android Variable, $15/hour avg Sweatcoin Digital currency for steps iOS and Android Up to $20/month Evidation Points for health actions, 10,000 pts = $10 iOS and Android 10,000 pts = $10 HealthyWage Cash for weight loss goals iOS and Android Varies on bet/goal Want to suggest improvements ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet From Shared Scooter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/internet-from-shared-scooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 15:54:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/internet-from-shared-scooter/</guid>
      <description>Get Internet Access Using an Electric Scooter SIM Card Notes: While the methods described in this guide may be technically feasible, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the use of someone else&amp;rsquo;s SIM card without proper authorization may be illegal or unethical. Always ensure you are complying with local laws and regulations when accessing the internet.
Living a nomadic or transient lifestyle doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to sacrifice internet connectivity. In fact, with the increasing prevalence of electric scooters equipped with IoT trackers in cities worldwide, you can harness the power of these devices to gain access to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trashback Rewards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/trashback-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:57:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/trashback-rewards/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Money with TrashBack Estimated Attention Time: Up-to-you
Estimated Income: Unknown
TrashBack is an application that allows you to earn gifts by helping the planet. With TrashBack, you can contribute to cleaning up the environment while also being rewarded for your efforts. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the process of using the TrashBack app to make money with trash.
Table of Contents Getting Started Exploring and Collecting Trash Earning Points Redeeming Points for Gifts Becoming a TrashBack Partner Contacting TrashBack Getting Started Download the TrashBack App: Visit your app store (available for free) and search for &amp;ldquo;TrashBack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweatcoin Walking Rewards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sweatcoin-walking-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:50:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sweatcoin-walking-rewards/</guid>
      <description>How to Earn Money with Sweatcoin Estimated Attention Time: 10 minutes / month
Estimated Income: 0.1€ / month
Sweatcoin is a popular app that allows you to earn digital currency, known as Sweatcoins, by simply walking and being active. In this tutorial, you will learn how to earn money with Sweatcoin and maximize your earnings.
Prerequisites Before we begin, make sure you have the following:
A smartphone (iOS or Android) Internet connectivity The Sweatcoin app downloaded from sweatco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bat Brave Rewards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bat-brave-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bat-brave-rewards/</guid>
      <description>How to Generate Income through Basic Attention Token (BAT) Estimated Attention Time: ~ 1-2 hours / month
Expected Earnings: ~ $5-10 worth of BAT / month.
In this tutorial, you will learn how to generate income through Basic Attention Token (BAT) using the Brave browser. BAT is a cryptocurrency that rewards users for their attention and engagement with digital advertising.
Step 1: Download and Install Brave Browser Go to the Brave browser website and download the browser for your operating system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate Passive incomes with your cryptos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/stacking-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/stacking-crypto/</guid>
      <description>Make Money by Stacking Crypto Estimated Attention Time: ~ 2-4 hours / month
Potential Earnings: up to 12%
Varies based on investment and market conditions
Introduction Cryptocurrency stacking, also known as staking, is a method of earning passive income by participating in the validation and security of blockchain networks. By staking your crypto assets, you contribute to the network&amp;rsquo;s operations and, in return, receive rewards in the form of additional cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Crow workers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/get-crow-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/get-crow-workers/</guid>
      <description>Get Crow Workers: How to Train Crows to Bring Objects Introduction Crows are highly intelligent birds that can be trained to perform various tasks. One fascinating task is training them to bring objects to humans, you can even train them to bring money. This tutorial will guide you through the process, which can be both enjoyable and help foster trust between humans and crows.
Materials You can also use a crow box to train the crow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Paid for housekeeping</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/get-paid-for-housekeeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/get-paid-for-housekeeping/</guid>
      <description>House Sitting: A Guide to Making Money Estimated Attention Time: ~ 20 hours / month
Expected Earnings: Up to $1,500/month
House sitting offers a unique opportunity to earn money while enjoying the comforts of a home away from home. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to supplement your income or embark on a flexible side gig, this tutorial will guide you through the process of making money through house sitting.
Table of Contents Introduction Finding House Sitting Opportunities Building a Strong Profile Nailing the Application Process Preparing for House Sitting Assignments Excelling as a House Sitter Expanding Your House Sitting Network Conclusion 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get paid to collect trashes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-trashback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-trashback/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Money with TrashBack Estimated Attention Time: Up-to-you
Estimated Income: Unknown
TrashBack is an application that allows you to earn gifts by helping the planet. With TrashBack, you can contribute to cleaning up the environment while also being rewarded for your efforts. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the process of using the TrashBack app to make money with trash.
Table of Contents Getting Started Exploring and Collecting Trash Earning Points Redeeming Points for Gifts Becoming a TrashBack Partner Contacting TrashBack Getting Started Download the TrashBack App: Visit your app store (available for free) and search for &amp;ldquo;TrashBack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get paid to learn about crypto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/learn-and-earn-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/learn-and-earn-crypto/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Money with Crypto Learn and Earn Programs Estimated Attention Time: 10 Minutes / Quizz
Potential Income: ~ 1.5€ / Quizz
Introduction Wondering how to make money with bitcoin? Want to earn cryptocurrency for watching videos? Being paid in crypto just for learning about it can sound too good to be true, but it’s not the case. Learn and earn crypto programs are designed to incentivize users to learn about cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology while earning rewards in the form of various cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get paid to solve git issues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-solving-git-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-solving-git-issues/</guid>
      <description>Sure, here is a shorter and more straightforward guide to making money with Gitpay:
Earn money by solving open-source issues on Gitpay:
Browse open-source projects and identify issues that you can solve Propose solutions and attach your Git commits to the issue Once your solution is approved, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive a bounty payment Earn money by providing freelance services for open-source projects:
Create a profile on Gitpay or similar platforms Offer your skills and expertise to open-source projects Bid on projects and negotiate project terms Once you complete a project, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive payment Earn money by accepting donations for your open-source contributions:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sell your data to Google</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-google-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:46:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-make-money-google-rewards/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Money with Google Opinion Rewards Estimated Attention Time: 10 minutes / month
Estimated Income: 0.1€ / month
Google Opinion Rewards is a mobile app created by the Google Surveys team that allows you to earn Google Play credit by answering short surveys. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the process of getting started with Google Opinion Rewards and maximizing your earning potential.
Step 1: Download and Install the App Open the Google Play Store on your Android device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Opinion Rewards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-opinion-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-opinion-rewards/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Money with Google Opinion Rewards Estimated Attention Time: 10 minutes / month
Estimated Income: 0.1€ / month
Google Opinion Rewards is a mobile app created by the Google Surveys team that allows you to earn Google Play credit by answering short surveys. In this tutorial, we will guide you through the process of getting started with Google Opinion Rewards and maximizing your earning potential.
Step 1: Download and Install the App Open the Google Play Store on your Android device.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
